I didn't know that
لم أكن أعرف ذلك
my empress was so charming.
كانت إمبراطوريتي ساحرة للغاية.
Just a few days after I left the palace,
بعد أيام قليلة من مغادرتي القصر ،
I already have Lan Yan's bosom friend.
لدي بالفعل صديق حضن لان يان.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
if you say that,
اذا قلت هذا،
I would think His Majesty is jealous.
أعتقد أن جلالة الملك يشعر بالغيرة.
If I'm really jealous,
إذا كنت غيورًا حقًا ،
what about Her Highness?
ماذا عن صاحبة السمو؟
If Your Majesty likes to be jealous,
إذا جلالتك تحب أن تغار ،
I'll ask Pearl to cook tomorrow.
سأطلب من بيرل أن تطبخ غدًا.
Add more vinegar,
أضف المزيد من الخل ،
and,
و،
Since His Majesty is outside the palace now,
بما أن جلالة الملك خارج القصر الآن ،
don't let me come and go.
لا تدعني أذهب وأذهب.
So as not to reveal his identity.
حتى لا يكشف عن هويته.
After the empress left the palace,
بعد أن غادرت الإمبراطورة القصر ،
she became bolder and bolder.
أصبحت أكثر جرأة وجرأة.
Of course.
بالطبع بكل تأكيد.
It's on my turf now.
إنه على أرضي الآن.
You can't be pushed around by me.
لا يمكنك أن أتحرك من قبلي.
How does Her Highness want to manipulate me?
كيف تريد سموها التلاعب بي؟
Su Jinxia,
سو جينشيا ،
this is a battle of dignity,
هذه معركة كرامة
We can't lose.
لا يمكننا أن نخسر.
Let's see what new tricks you have.
دعونا نرى ما هي الحيل الجديدة التي لديك.
It's only been a few days,
لقد مرت بضعة أيام فقط ،
but the anti-flirting trick doesn't work.
لكن الحيلة المضادة للمغازلة لا تعمل.
Oh,
أوه،
I admit defeat.
أعترف بالهزيمة.
I won't mess with you anymore.
لن العبث معك بعد الآن.
Your wound is bleeding.
جرحك ينزف.
Let me bandage it for you.
اسمحوا لي أن ضمادة لك.
I knew the empress
كنت أعرف الإمبراطورة
had been coveting my body for a long time.
كان يشتهي جسدي لفترة طويلة.
You don't have to take the initiative.
ليس عليك أن تأخذ زمام المبادرة.
You darned monster.
أنت مرتبك الوحش.
Have you gained weight recently?
هل اكتسبت وزنا مؤخرا؟
Ah,
آه،
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
Why do you say that?
لماذا تقول هذا؟
Then why are you getting more and more important
إذن لماذا تزداد أهمية أكثر فأكثر
in my heart.
في قلبي.
I can't stand you.
لا أطيقك.
I didn't expect that we started to play local love words in ancient times.
لم أكن أتوقع أننا بدأنا نلعب كلمات الحب المحلية في العصور القديمة.
What kind of local love words?
أي نوع من كلمات الحب المحلية؟
I'll scratch you to death.
سأخدشك حتى الموت.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Does it hurt?
هل تؤلم؟
I lied to you.
لقد كذبت عليك.
She stayed by my side all night.
بقيت بجانبي طوال الليل.
After I met her,
بعد أن قابلتها ،
I couldn't help but want to laugh.
لا يسعني إلا أن أضحك.
Pearl,
لؤلؤة،
you're here.
أنت هنا.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
Childe Qin.
تشايلد تشين.
I'm your lady's husband.
أنا زوج سيدتك.
Just call me uncle.
فقط اتصل بي عمي.
Yes.
نعم.
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
your lady was exhausted last night.
سيدتك كانت منهكة الليلة الماضية.
Don't wake her up.
لا توقظيها.
Boss didn't sleep in the same bed
لم ينام الرئيس في نفس السرير
with skinny hemp stalks last night, did he?
مع سيقان القنب النحيفة الليلة الماضية ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Did I call Miss?
هل اتصلت بالسيدة؟
Fight with me.
قاتل معي.
You're not qualified.
أنت غير مؤهل.